<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Insights - Hologuti Business Centre</title>
    <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/</link>
    <description>Insightful info on social interest, education application, health and technology</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <!-- Add items for each article -->
    <item>
      <title>The 3MTT Job Opportunity</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <p>The <b>3 Million Technical Talent (3MTT)</b> program is a pivotal initiative under the <em>Federal Ministry of Communication, Innovation and Digital Economy &#40;FMCIDE&#41;</em> in Nigeria, aimed at harnessing and developing the vast tech talent within the country, through comprehensive training, mentorship, and support, which will foster a culture of innovation that will contribute to the digital economy of Nigeria and putting Nigeria technical talents at the global level. In achieving its desired goal, the 3MTT had lunched <b>3mtt JobBoard platform</b>. This platform offers a unique opportunity to connect job applicants to hiring companies.</p>
        <p>The platform is specifically designed to make the job search process easier and more efficient for both job seekers and hiring companies, and to also give individual who had participated in the 3MTT initail programe, an enviroment to deploy their skills. Interested individuals are employed to explore the <i>3mtt JobBoard portal</i>, create a profile to benefit in the exciting opportunity.</p>
        <p>Current Openings and How to Apply:</p>
        <ol>
          <li>Visit the official 3MTTportal to <a href="https://3mtt.seamlesshiring.com/">sign up.</a></li>
          <li>Browse the list of hiring company and available positions.</li>
          <li>Select the role that aligns with your qualifications.</li>
          <li>Submit your application along with your resume and any required documents.</li>
        </ol>
        <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/vB4c7zb2/3mtt-400x400.jpg">
         ]]>
        </description>
        <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/technology/threeTT</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

                  <!-- Article 2-->
    <item>
      <title>Federal Government MSME and Manufacturing Businesses Loan</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
           <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/Prd0JWD6/federal-grant-loan-1.webp">
           <h1>The Federal Government Lunches Loan Application for MSME And Manufacturing Segment of The Presidential 200 Billion Naira Fund</h1>
           <article>
            <section>
             <p>The Federal Government of Nigeria is set to disburse funds to <i>Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises,</i>  and the <i>Manufacturing Businesses as well.</i> This announcement was made known by the <b>Honourable Minister Dr. Doris Nkiruka Uzoka-Anite MD, CFA</b>, through one of her official social handle accounts.</p>
             <p>The Federal Government of Nigeria has recently started funds disbursement to applicants who applied under the <em>Presidential Conditional Grant Scheme (now closed)</em>, to support nano businesses, to revitalize businesses that have been harmfully affected by economic challenges. The Government has further taken a bold step towards promoting the growth of businesses and job creation in the country by launching the <strong>MSME and Manufacturing Fund</strong>, to provide much needed financial support to businesses in these key sectors.</p>
             <p>The government has allocated 75 billion naira to each sector. Under the MSME component of the fund, enterprises are eligible to receive up to 1 million naira in loans, while manufacturing companies can access loans of up to 1 billion naira. This injection of capital will enable businesses to expand their operations, grow their businesses, create jobs, and contribute to the overall economic development of the country.</p>
            </section>
            <section class="criteria">
              <img src="/assets/eligibility.jpg" alt="eligibility">
              <h2>Eligibility and Application Process</h2>
              <div>
               <h3>The Loan Eligibility Criteria (for MSME loan up to 1 million Naira)</h3>
               <ul>
                <span>A&#41;. Eligibility Criteria: -</span>
                 <ul>
                  <li>Must be an existing business in operation for at least one year, or a registered start-up.</li>
                  <li>Provide CAC registration documents.</li>
                  <li>Present company's Bank Statement for existing businesses or Chief Promoter's Bank Statement for start-up.</li>
                  <li>Fulfil required monthly turnover and comply with other requirements specified by the bank.</li>
                 </ul>
                 </ul>
                 <ul>
                  <span>B&#41;. Security: -</span>
                  <ul>
                   <li>Provide a Personal Guarantee of the promoter</li>
                   <li>Agree to BVN convenant</li>
                   <li>Adhere to Global Standing Instruction (GSI) and other securities as required by the bank</li>
                  </ul>
                 </ul>
                 <ul>
                  <span>C&#41;. Repayment Frequency: -</span>
                   <ul>
                    <li>Monthly equal instalments with no moratorium, spanning a 3-year term.</li>
                   </ul>
                  </ul>
               </div>
                  <div>
                    <h3>For Manufacturers (For Loans up to 1 Billion Naira)</h3>
                    <ul>
                      <li>Choose between Working Capital or Asset Financing.</li>
                      <li>Maintain at least a 6-month business/corporate banking relationship.</li>
                      <li>Provide additional documentation as required by the bank.</li>
                      <li>Asset Financing comes with a 5-year repayment period, and Working Capital Financing includes a 6-month moratorium on principal and interest, followed by a 12-month equal. instalment repayment plan.</li>
                    </ul>
                  </div>
              </section>
              <Section>
                <p>The ministry invites all eligible enterprises to join this transformative</p>
                <a href="https://loan.fedgrantandloan.gov.ng/" target="_blank">Apply Here</a>
              </Section>
           </article>
          ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/interest/FG-large-and-MSME_loan</link>
      <PubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:00:00 GTM</PubDate>
    </item>

                  <!-- Article 3-->
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria lunches Credit facilitating platform</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
            <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/mgRszqzz/Credi-Corp-removebg-preview.png">
            <h1>Nigeria Consumer Credit Corporation (CrediCorp)</h1>
            <p>Nigeria lunches Credit facilitating platform, <b>Nigeria Consumer Credit Corporation (CrediCorp)</b>. The company is owned by the Federal Government of Nigeria with the primary goal of increasing access to consumer credit for 50% of the working population in Nigeria by 2030.</p>
             <p><b>CrediCorp</b> focuses on strategies that addresses barriers to accessing credit. IT is dedicated to collaborating with key stakeholders such as the Central Bank of Nigeria and various entities within the financial sector, providing capital and guarantees.</p>
             <p>The corporation’s business operations concentrate on enhancing access to consumer credit in Nigeria. The corporation will implement a unifying credit registry using the <em>National Identification Number (NIN)</em>, to provide credit guarantees to financial institutions to accelerate people-centred credit products and incentive purchase of locally manufactured goods and services.</p>
             <p>The Credit scheme will roll out in two phases starting from <time datetime="2024-05-01"><b>May 2024</b></time>. The 1st phase is categorised into 3 sections which comprise <i>Federal, State Civil Servants and White collar & informal workers</i> (covering over 28 million population), to be completed in <time datetime="2024-12-31"><b>December 2024</b></time>. The 2nd phase which covers the <i>General public</i> (73 million population) will commence the following year.</p>
             <p>To register, visit CredCrop official <a href="https://www.credicorp.ng/">website</a>.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/interest/CrediCorp</link>
      <pubDate>Thurs, 25 Apr 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

                  <!-- Article 4-->
    <item>
      <title>New Deadline for Nigeria Diaspora Fund, Expression of Interest submission</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
           <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/Prd0JWD6/federal-grant-loan-1.webp">
           <h1>Federal Ministry of Industry, Trade, and Investment announces New Deadline for Nigeria Diaspora Fund Expression of Interest</h1> 
           <article>
              <p>The <em>Federal Ministry of Industry, Trade, and Investment</em> wishes to inform stakeholders that the deadline for the submission of <b>Expressions of Interest (EOI)</b> for the Nigeria Diaspora Fund has been extended to <time datetime="2024-05-13"><b>13th May 2024</b></time>. The extension has been granted considering the need for all stakeholders to have adequate time to prepare and submit their application within the set guidelines for the $10 billion Nigeria Diaspora Fund.</p>
              <p>Notably, the EOI opportunity is open to Fund Managers who are interested in contributing to the creation of a multisectoral, multilateral private sector-led investment fund. Prospective applicants are strongly advised to use the additional time to refine their submissions to ensure that their assessments meet all the.</p>
              <p>For further information, please visit the official website at <a href="https://nigeriadiasporafund.gov.ng/" class="official-web"> www.nigeriadiasporafund.gov.ng</a></p>
            </article>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/interest/EOI-extension</link>
      <pubDate>fri, 3 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

                <!-- Article 5-->
     <item>
      <title>How to Check JAMB 2024 Result</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
           <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/NjKxY5gT/JAMB-2024-RESULT.png"> 
           <h1>JAMB clarifies candidates on the only way to check 2024 UTME Result</h1>
           <article>
            <p>The <b>Joint Admissions and Matriculation Board</b> clarifies to candidates the only way to check the 2024 UTME results, contrary to the claims circulating on social media, where some individuals are flaunting printed result slips.</p>
            <p>In previous years, candidates could access their results through the Board’s website. However, the procedure for checking the 2024 UTME results has changed; unlike before, the results  <b><em>are not available</em></b>  in hard format currently and <b><em>cannot not be accessed</em></b> on the Board’s website. Candidates are advised to be wary of any person who makes such a claim.</p>
            <p>The Board instructs the public that the only way to check the 2024 UTME results is by sending <b class="sending-UTME">‘UTMERESULT’ to 55019 or 66019</b>  using the same phone number that the candidate used for UTME registration.</p>
            <p><i>Additionally, candidates wishing to access services provided by the Board, other than the UTME, must create a profile by sending their NIN to 55019 or 66019 from the phone number they intend to use for all Board-related communications.</i></p>
            <p>Therefore, the public is advised to avoid using third-party services for result retrieval and is urged to follow the method specified by the Board to access results.</p>
          </article>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/education/jamb-2024-result</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 6 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

              <!-- Article 6-->
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria's Student Loan Scheme</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
           <main>
            <div class="intro">
              <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/tTkzk47t/nelf-logo.jpg" alt="nelf logo">
              <h1>Nigeria's Student Loan Application Portal</h1>
            </div>
            <hr>
            <article>
              <p>In a significant move to bolster higher education and alleviate the financial burden on students, the Federal Government of Nigeria is set to launch the long-awaited <b>Student Loan Scheme</b>. After a period of anticipation and meticulous planning, the government is set to officially open the <em>student loan application portal</em> which is said to commence on <time datetime="2024-05-24"><b>May 24th, 2024</b></time>.</p>
              <p>This groundbreaking initiative aims to provide a lifeline to students across the nation, ensuring that financial constraints do not hinder the pursuit of academic excellence. The scheme is designed to be inclusive, catering to a wide range of students who aspire to further their education but lack the necessary resources.</p>
              <p>As the launch date approaches, students are encouraged to prepare and to take advantage of this opportunity. The scheme is not just a financial arrangement; it is a beacon of hope, symbolizing the government's resolve to empower the youth through education.</p>
              <p>The Federal Government of Nigeria invites all eligible students to mark their calendars for <time datetime="2024-05-24"><b>May 24th, 2024</b></time>, and join in ushering in a new era of accessible education financing by visiting <a href="https://nelf.gov.ng/" target="_blank" class="nelf">nelf.gov.ng</a>. Stay tuned for more updates as we approach the launch of this transformative program.</p>
            </article>
          </main>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/education/2-FG-student-loan</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

              <!-- Article 7-->
     <item>
      <title>NECO Important Notice</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <main>
            <div class="headline">
              <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/NFbc4hX4/neco-logo-372.jpg" alt="NECO logo">
              <h1>National Examinations Council (NECO) Issues Important Clarification</h1>
            </div>
            <article>
              <p><b>The National Examinations Council (NECO)</b> has issued an important clarification regarding the <i>2024 Senior School Certificate Examination (SSCE) Internal Registration</i> process. Contrary to rumours circulating on social media, NECO confirms that there has been <em>no extension to the registration deadline</em>.</p>
              <p>The official registration period commenced on <time datetime="2023-12-18">Monday, December 18, 2023</time>, and is set to conclude on <time datetime="2024-06-03">Monday, June 3, 2024</time>. Following this, a late registration window is available from Tuesday, June 4, 2024, to Monday, June 10, 2024, which will include a late registration fee. </p>
              <p>NECO urges all involved parties to ignore any misinformation suggesting an extension of the registration deadline to Monday, June 20, 2024. The council emphasizes the importance of adhering to the announced dates to ensure a smooth and orderly examination process.</p>
              <p>The 2024 SSCE Internal is scheduled to start on <time datetime="2024-06-19">June 19, 2024</time>, and will run until <time datetime="2024-07-26"> July 26, 2024</time>. During this period, candidates will have the opportunity to showcase their knowledge across an extensive array of 76 subjects. For the latest updates and official announcements, always refer to NECO's official channels.</p>
            </article>
          </main>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/education/e3-neco-important-notice</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>

              <!-- Article 8-->
    <item>
      <title>Rural Area Programme on Investment and Development</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <main>
            <div class="headline">
              <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/2S4zYWMM/RAPID.png" alt="RAPID logo">
              <h1>Empowering Rural Entrepreneurs Initiative By The Bank of Industry</h1>
            </div>
            <article>
              <p>The Federal Government, in collaboration with the <i>Bank of Industry (BOI)</i>, has unveiled the <b>Rural Area Programme on Investment and Development (RAPID)</b>, a strategic initiative designed to bolster youth and women-led enterprises in Nigeria's underserved communities.</p>
              <p>The RAPID scheme is set to inject vital capital and open new avenues for rural populations, directly confronting the persistent issue of rural-urban migration. The program's core objective is to promote economic inclusivity, ensuring that residents of rural areas have fair access to financial resources.</p>
              <p>In a significant move, the BOI has pledged robust financial backing, with potential grants reaching up to 10 million naira for each qualifying project. The focus is on aiding existing small-scale businesses that are poised for growth, as well as nurturing new ventures, particularly those led by youth and women entrepreneurs. Beneficiaries can expect a three-year repayment window complemented by a six-month grace period, all at an accommodating interest rate of 5%.</p>
              <p>The pilot phase of RAPID is set to benefit a select group of 10 entrepreneurs from each state, including the Federal Capital Territory, culminating in a total of 370 recipients.</p>
              <p>To maximize the program's reach, interested parties can apply through a specially designated online platform or in person at any BOI district office across the nation.</p>
              <p>Prospective applicants should note that the registration portal, accessible at <a href="https://rapid.boi.ng/register" target="_blank">rapid.boi.ng/register</a>, will close on <time datetime="2024-05-29">May 29th</time>. Potential candidates are encouraged to act swiftly to take advantage of this opportunity.</p>
            </article>
          </main>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/interest/i4_FG-RAPID</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

                    <!-- Article 9-->
    <item>
      <title>CAC Alternative Registration Platform For POS Agents</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <main>
            <div class="headline">
              <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/6qpwKMmx/cac-logo.png">
              <h1>CAC Provides Additional Way for Bank and Fintech to Navigate the Agents Registration Process</h1>
            </div>
            <article>
              <p> In a significant move to streamline the operations of financial technology (fintech) services, the <b>Corporate Affairs Commission (CAC)</b> has mandated all bank and fintech Point of Sale (POS) agents to register as business entities. This directive, issued earlier this month, aims to formalize the rapidly growing sector, and ensure compliance with regulatory standards.</p>
              <p>Understanding the potential complexities this new requirement may introduce, the <abbr title="Corporate Affairs Commission">CAC</abbr> has thoughtfully provided alternative means for registration, thereby simplifying the process for agents. According to a recent statement released by the Commission, <q>in order to ease compliance with this directive, the Commission has deployed alternative platforms for quick registration of the Agents.</q></p>
              <div class="options-wrapper">
                <span class="two-distinct">The alternatives presented offer two distinct options for registration:</span>
                <p><b class="option">Option 1</b> <br>outlines a more traditional approach, where customers can download the Business Name Registration form, make the necessary payments through Remita, and submit the required documents via email to <a href="mailto:quickservice@cac.gov.ng">quickservice@cac.gov.ng</a>. It's important to note that by choosing this option, <q>you also consent that CAC may alter your proposed name(s) where necessary to ensure approval</q>, should there be any issues with the submitted names.</p>
                <p><b class="option">Option 2</b> <br> leverages technology to expedite the process, allowing customers to collaborate with their fintech institutions, which can handle name reservation and registration through API integrations with the <abbr title="Corporate Affairs Commission">CAC</abbr> portal. This method is touted as <q>the fastest and most convenient for end-users</q>, streamlining the process significantly.</p>
              </div>
              <p>The Commission's proactive approach in providing these alternatives before the registration deadline of <time datetime="2024-07-07">7th July 2024</time> demonstrates a commitment to fostering a supportive environment for fintech operations while maintaining the necessary oversight.</p>
              <p>For fintech POS agents, this development represents a crucial step towards greater legitimacy and operational efficiency. It also reflects the broader trend of digital transformation within the Nigerian financial sector, where technology is increasingly being harnessed to improve services and regulatory compliance.</p>
              <p>As the deadline approaches, agents are encouraged to evaluate both options and choose the one that best suits their needs, ensuring a smooth transition into compliance with the <abbr title="Corporate Affairs Commission">CAC's</abbr> directives. The future of fintech in Nigeria is bright, and these measures are a testament to the country's dedication to nurturing a robust and responsible digital economy.</p>
            </article>
          </main>       
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/bankretail/b1-CAC_alternative_registration_for_POS</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

                  <!-- Article 10 -->
    <item>
      <title>Federal Government of Nigeria RENEWED HOPE HOUSING DELIVERY PORTAL</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <main>
            <div class="headline">
              <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/Kc9207G9/renewed-hope-home-logo.png" alt="renewed hope home logo">
              <h1>Unveiling a Path to Homeownership in Nigeria</h1>
            </div>
            <article>
              <p>The dream of homeownership can feel distant for many Nigerians, particularly those in the low-and middle-income brackets. However, a recent initiative by the Federal Government of Nigeria offers a beacon of hope. The <q>Renewed Hope Estates and Cities</q> program, launched by the <i>Ministry of Housing and Urban Development</i> under <i><b>Arc. Ahmed Musa Dangiwa</b></i>, aims to bridge the housing gap and make owning a home a more achievable reality.</p>
              <p>The program recognizes the significant housing deficit in Nigeria. With <b>100,000</b> new housing units planned for construction across all <b>36 states</b> and the <b>FCT</b>, the initiative seeks to make a substantial impact. The variety of ownership options offered further strengthens its reach. Homeowners can choose from outright purchase, mortgage financing, or a rent-to-own scheme, catering to diverse financial circumstances.</p>
              <p>A commendable aspect of the program is its specific focus on low- and mid-income earners. This segment of the population has often faced significant challenges in securing affordable housing. The <q>Renewed Hope Estates and Cities</q> program extends a helping hand to both Nigerians residing within the country and those living abroad.</p>
              <p>
                <span class="access">Accessibility</span><br>
                The program's transparency is a positive step. Nigerians interested in participating in the program can visit the official portal, <a href="https://renewedhopehomes.fmhud.gov.ng" target="_blank" class="link-to-renewedHope">renewedhopehomes.fmhud.gov.ng</a>, to explore available options, eligibility requirements, and application procedures. The application allows for easy access to information and potentially simplifies the application process. This online platform can be crucial for those seeking clarity on eligibility criteria and application procedures.
              </p>
              <p>While the program is still in its early stages, it has the potential to be a significant force for positive change in Nigeria's housing market. Increased access to affordable housing can contribute to greater social stability and economic growth.</p>
              <p>The  <q>Renewed Hope Estates and Cities</q> presents a promising opportunity for many Nigerians to achieve their dream of homeownership. Let's hope it lives up to its name and ushers in a new era of accessible housing for the nation.</p>
              <p>
                <span class="informing">Staying Informed</span> <br>  
                As the program unfolds, it's important to stay informed about updates, eligibility requirements, and the application process. We can expect more details to emerge in the coming days and weeks. Following more reliable sources, such as the Federal Ministry of Housing and Urban Development website, will be key.</p>
            </article>
          </main>        
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/interest/i5_FG-home-scheme</link>
      <pubDate>Thurs, 23 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>

                  <!-- Article 11 -->
    <item>
      <title>How to Apply for Nigerian Student Loan Fund</tittle>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <main>
            <div class="headline">
                <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/tTwNXC4f/nelf-logo.jpg" atl="NELFund logo">
                <h1>Nigerian Student Loan Application Step-by-step </h1>
            </div>
            <article>
              <p>The chance to pursue higher education with financial backing is finally here! <br> The Federal Government of Nigeria, through the <b>Nigerian Education Loan Fund (NELFUND)</b>, officially launched the Student Loan Scheme portal today, <time datetime="2024-05-24">May 24th, 2024</time>.</p>
              <p>This is fantastic news for students and those who may have previously faced financial barriers to attending university or college. Now, you can apply for a loan to cover your educational expenses!</p>
              <section>
                <h1>How to Apply:</h1>
                <p>The application process is straightforward and can be completed online. Here's a quick breakdown, thanks to <a href="https://x.com/PBATMediaCentre?t=kWy65YYIe0lZNO_FZF3fug&s=09" aria-label="X (formally twitter) account of President BAT Media Centre" target="_blank">@PBATMediaCentre</a> for the info.</p>
                <ul style="background-color: #fffafa;">
                  <span class="steps">1. Create an Account:</span>
                  <li>Visit <a href="https://nelf.gov.ng/" target="_blank">https://nelf.gov.ng/</a> and click <q>Apply Now</q></li>
                  <li>Answer the questions, confirming you're a Nigerian citizen.</li>
                  <li>Verify your educational information by selecting your school and providing your matriculation number.</li>
                  <li>Create an account with your email address and password. Verify your email when prompted.</li>
                  <img src="https://i.postimg.cc/pXhZ1P24/Screenshot.png" alt="Screenshot of the 'create a page'">
                </ul>
                <ul style="background-color: #f5f5f5;">
                  <span class="steps">2. Complete Your Profile:</span>
                  <li>Log in with your email and password.</li>
                  <li>Update your contact details, educational details (institution and matric number), and verify your Bank Verification Number (BVN).</li>
                </ul>
                <ul style="background-color: #fffafa;">
                  <span class="steps">3. Apply for the Loan:</span>
                  <li>Click <q>Request for Student Loan</q> on the homepage.</li>
                  <li>Select what type of loan you need (institutional charges only or including upkeep).</li>
                  <li>Upload supporting documents like your admission letter (mandatory) and student ID/institution invoice (optional).</li>
                  <li>Agree to the terms and conditions, then submit your application.</li>
                  <li>Track the status of your application under the <q>Loans</q> section.</li>
                </ul>
              </section>
            </article>
          </main>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <link>https://insights.hologutibusinesscentre.com/education/E4-student-loan-official-lunch</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
